flaunt.com 2016-05-11

# Flaunt Magazine | Privacy Policy & Cookies Statement

### Collection of Information

In various ways we collect information that is volunteered by visitors to our site. Certain identifying information, such as name, street address, city, state, zip code and email address, is gathered at certain interactive areas on the site, such as when you subscribe to our print or digital publication while online. Wherever possible and practical, we give users options about submitting information.

### Use of Collected Information

With respect to advertisements, an advertiser will inform us which type of audience it seeks to reach, and we may place advertisements on Flaunt.com that fit the advertiser’s criteria. Pop-up advertisements may be displayed to a targeted audience on Flaunt.com based on these criteria. The advertisers are not permitted to access your account or any of your personally identifiable information.  
We also use tracking information to determine which areas of our site users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas.  
We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their interests. We do not track the usage patterns of individual users, so an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked on a particular ad.

### Information Sharing

When you visit Flaunt.com and are asked to provide information about yourself, you are sharing that information only with us, unless specifically stated otherwise in this Privacy Policy or as stated in any notice given to you at the time the information was requested. We will not disclose the information you submit, except as described here in, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure to protect our rights or property, or for administrative or other purposes we deem necessary to maintain or service our products and services. For example, we may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide you with our services.  
If you do not want your data to be shared, you may choose not to permit the data to be collected or transferred by not submitting personally identifiable information on our site, or by not using a particular service.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
